<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LokaTraave</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="LOGIN_APP_TEXT">LokaTravel</string>
    <string name="EMAIL">Email</string>
    <string name="PASSWORD">Password</string>
    <string name="LOGIN_TEXT">Login</string>
    <string name="ERROR_EMAIL_EMPTY">Name cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="ERROR_EMAIL_INVALID_FORMAT">The email format entered is invalid</string>
    <string name="ERROR_EMAIL_ALREADY_REGISTERED">This email is already registere</string>
    <string name="HINT_EMAIL">Enter Your Email</string>
    <string name="ERROR_PASSWORD_EMPTY">Password cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="ERROR_PASSWORD_LENGTH">Password must be at least 8 characters</string>
    <string name="ERROR_PASSWORD_MISMATCH">Password and confirm password do not match</string>
    <string name="HINT_PASSWORD">Enter Your Password</string>
    <string name="WELCOME_LOGIN_TEXT">Welcome\n</string>
    <string name="MSG_LOGIN">Welcome To LokaTravel</string>
    <string name="WELCOME_REGISTER_TEXT">Create account</string>
    <string name="MSG_REGISTER">Get the best out of derleng by creating an account</string>
    <string name="FULL_NAME">Full name</string>
    <string name="ERROR_NAME_EMPTY">Name cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="ERROR_NAME_TOOLONG">Name cannot exceed 25 characters</string>
    <string name="HINT_FULL_NAME">Enter Full Name</string>
    <string name="HINT_CONFIRM_PASSWORD">Enter Your Password</string>
    <string name="CONFIRM_PASSWORD">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="REGISTER_APP_TEXT">LokaTravel</string>
    <string name="REGISTER_TEXT">Register</string>
    <string name="TermCondition">I accept term and condition</string>
    <string name="INFO_REGISTER_TEXT">Dont Have an Account?\n</string>
    <string name="INFO_LOGIN_TEXT">Already Have an Account?</string>
    <string name="COPYRIGHT">LokaTravel Right Reserved</string>
    <string name="welcomeText">Discovering Indonesia: Nature and Culture Unveiled</string>
    <string name="search">Search\n</string>
    <string name="HOME_TEXT">Discovering Indonesia: Nature and Culture Unveiled</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile\n</string>
    <string name="news">News\n</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="PROFILE">PROFILE</string>
    <string name="INFO">Other Information</string>
    <string name="REPORT_BUG">Report Bug\n</string>
    <string name="LOGOUT">Log Out</string>
    <string name="LAST_LOGIN">Last Login</string>
    <string name="ERROR_PASSWORD_NOTSAME">The password or email you entered is incorrect</string>
    <string name="ERROR_EDITEXT_EMPTY">Please fill in all fields correctly</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key">com.example.lokatravel.PREFERENCE_FILE_KEY</string>
    <string name="saved_login_status_key">com.example.lokatravel.PREFERENCE_FILE_KEY</string>
    <string name="saved_name_key">saved</string>
    <string name="saved_email_key">saved\n</string>
    <string name="show_password">Show Password</string>
    <string name="back">back\n</string>
    <string name="saved_profile_image_key">Image\n</string>
    <string name="report_bug">Report Bug\n</string>
    <string name="logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="save_changes">\nSave Changes</string>
    <string name="enter_name">FullName\n</string>
    <string name="profile_image">Profile\n</string>
    <string name="sample_email">Email\n\n</string>
    <string name="info">Info\n</string>
    <string name="Save">Save\n</string>
    <string name="wisata_image">Image Wisata\n</string>
    <string name="CHANGE_PASSWORD">Change Password\n</string>
    <string name="saved_password_key">Saved Password\n</string>
    <string name="normal_type">Normal</string>
    <string name="satellite_type">Satellite</string>
    <string name="terrain_type">Terrain</string>
    <string name="hybrid_type">Hybrid</string>
    <string name="string_terms">Welcome to LokaTravel!\n\nThese terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of [Nama Aplikasi], operated by LokaTravel.\n\nBy accessing this application, we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use LokaTavel if you do not agree to all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.\n\n1. Definitions\n\nApplication: refers to LokaTravel.\nWe/Us/Our: refers to LokaTravel.\nUser/You: refers to any individual accessing or using the Application.\nContent: refers to text, images, graphics, data, or other information available within the Application.\n2. Use of the Application\n\n2.1 Eligibility: You must be at least 18 years old to use this Application. By using this Application, you represent and warrant that you meet this requirement.\n\n2.2 License: We grant you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited license to use the Application in accordance with these Terms.\n\n2.3 User Obligations: You agree to use the Application only for lawful purposes and in a way that does not infringe the rights of, restrict, or inhibit anyone else\'s use and enjoyment of the Application.\n\n3. User Accounts\n\n3.1 Account Creation: To access certain features of the Application, you may need to create an account. You agree to provide accurate, current, and complete information during the registration process and update such information to keep it accurate, current, and complete.\n\n3.2 Account Security: You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account credentials and for all activities that occur under your account. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account.\n\n4. Recommendations\n\n4.1 Accuracy: The Application provides recommendations based on algorithms and user preferences. While we strive to provide accurate and relevant recommendations, we do not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any recommendation.\n\n4.2 Responsibility: Users are solely responsible for their decisions based on the recommendations provided by the Application.\n\n5. Content\n\n5.1 User Content: Users may submit, upload, or otherwise make available content, including but not limited to reviews, comments, and ratings. You retain ownership of your content but grant us a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free license to use, distribute, reproduce, and display such content in connection with the Application.\n\n5.2 Prohibited Content: Users are prohibited from posting content that is unlawful, offensive, defamatory, or otherwise violates any laws or the rights of others.\n\n6. Intellectual Property\n\n6.1 Ownership: The Application and its original content, features, and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of LokaTravel and its licensors.\n\n6.2 Trademarks: All trademarks, service marks, and logos used in the Application are the trademarks of LokaTavel or their respective owners.\n\n7. Termination\n\nWe may terminate or suspend your access to the Application immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you breach these Terms.\n\n8. Limitation of Liability\n\nTo the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, LookaTrave shall not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages, or any loss of profits or revenues, whether incurred directly or indirectly, or any loss of data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your use or inability to use the Application; (ii) any unauthorized access to or use of our servers and/or any personal information stored therein.\n\n9. Governing Law\n\nThese Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Indonesia, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.\n\n10. Changes to Terms\n\nWe reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material, we will provide at least 30 days\' notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.\n\n11. Contact Us\n\nIf you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us at Attajr59@gmail.com.</string>
    <string name="todo">todo\n</string>
</resources>